<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NHL on Jeffrey Noh&#39;s Github</title>
    <link>/tags/nhl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NHL on Jeffrey Noh&#39;s Github</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/nhl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Who is the best player on Boston&#39;s top line?</title>
      <link>/2021/04/22/who-is-the-best-player-on-boston-s-top-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/04/22/who-is-the-best-player-on-boston-s-top-line/</guid>
      <description>The Boston Bruins drafted David Pastrnak in 2014. The impact that he would come to make with line mates, Brad Marchand and Patrice Bergeron, is something in the Boston organization that fans will remember for a very long time. It’s easy to think of all that they have accomplished together, but we will dive into which one, of the three players, have had the biggest impact and the best statistics playing together as the top line in Boston.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shooters Shoot</title>
      <link>/2021/04/01/shooters-shoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/04/01/shooters-shoot/</guid>
      <description>Picture this: you walk into your favorite NHL teams’ home ice rink. What is the first thing that you see? Probably the giant screens hanging above center ice known as a jumbotron. You examine the opponents’ statistics. As your eyes make their way down the list, you see a small box labeled “Shots.”
Most of the time you would overlook it and pay little to no attention to it, but when you look past the fact that it is just a number on a screen, and dig into the statistics, the number of shots is a very interesting category.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
